<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
	<ARKPPP_WirelessPowerReceptor.label>Приемник WPN</ARKPPP_WirelessPowerReceptor.label>
	<ARKPPP_WirelessPowerReceptor.description>Требуется подключить к действительной WPN для обеспечения питания.</ARKPPP_WirelessPowerReceptor.description>
	
	<ARKPPP_WirelessPortablePowerReceptor.label>Портативный приемник WPN</ARKPPP_WirelessPortablePowerReceptor.label>
	<ARKPPP_WirelessPortablePowerReceptor.description>Требуется подключить к действительной WPN для обеспечения питания. Мощность снижена из-за небольших габаритов.</ARKPPP_WirelessPortablePowerReceptor.description>
	
	<ARKPPP_WirelessPowerEmitter.label>Излучатель WPN</ARKPPP_WirelessPowerEmitter.label>
	<ARKPPP_WirelessPowerEmitter.description>A wireless power emitter device used to broadcast over long distance a WPN. Caution this device is sensitive to weather conditions (thunderstorms)</ARKPPP_WirelessPowerEmitter.description>
	
	<ARKPPP_WirelessPowerEmitterAdvanced.label>Advanced WPN emitter</ARKPPP_WirelessPowerEmitterAdvanced.label>
	<ARKPPP_WirelessPowerEmitterAdvanced.description>A wireless power emitter device used to broadcast over long distance a WPN.</ARKPPP_WirelessPowerEmitterAdvanced.description>
	
	<ARKPPP_LocalWirelessPowerEmitter.label>LWPN emitter</ARKPPP_LocalWirelessPowerEmitter.label>
	<ARKPPP_LocalWirelessPowerEmitter.description>A device used to build local (on the current map) wireless powergrid (LWPN), which allow to connect every electrical devices without cables</ARKPPP_LocalWirelessPowerEmitter.description>
	
	<ARKPPP_LocalWirelessPortablePowerEmitter.label>Portale LWPN emitter</ARKPPP_LocalWirelessPortablePowerEmitter.label>
	<ARKPPP_LocalWirelessPortablePowerEmitter.description>A portable device used to build local (on the current map) wireless powergrid (LWPN), which allow to connect every electrical devices without cables. Caution because of its small dimensions, it can handle limited wireless devices</ARKPPP_LocalWirelessPortablePowerEmitter.description>
	
	<ARKPPP_PowerBeamAbsorptionDish.label>Absorption Dish</ARKPPP_PowerBeamAbsorptionDish.label>
	<ARKPPP_PowerBeamAbsorptionDish.description>A giant absorption dish destined to gather power from the ancient satellites network</ARKPPP_PowerBeamAbsorptionDish.description>
	
	<ARKPPP_PowerBeamSatelliteTargetingSystem.label>Satellite Targeting System</ARKPPP_PowerBeamSatelliteTargetingSystem.label>
	<ARKPPP_PowerBeamSatelliteTargetingSystem.description>A supercomputer used to hack and control one of the ancient satellites. In addition to having to be constantly cooled, no abrupt desynchronization with the satellite should take place, because it can have very serious repercussions. Thus start and stop init sequences must always be respected !</ARKPPP_PowerBeamSatelliteTargetingSystem.description>

	<ARKPPP_ADRelayTower.label>AD relay tower</ARKPPP_ADRelayTower.label>
	<ARKPPP_ADRelayTower.description>Radio Antenna used to remotelly connect one or more "Absorrion Dishes"(ADs) to a Satelite Targetting System (STS) via the satelite network</ARKPPP_ADRelayTower.description>
</LanguageData>